<samba:parameter name="continuous availability"
                 context="S"
                 type="enum"
                 enumlist="enum_bool_auto"
                 xmlns:samba="http://www.samba.org/samba/DTD/samba-doc">
<description>
    <para>
    Continous Availability (CA) is a feature of the underlying file system.
    Generally speaking, CA may be available on clustered or distributed file
    systems that allow a connection to fail over to another node in the
    event of a server crash or reboot.
    </para>
    <para>
    Continuous availability is only enabled if Persistent Handle support has
    been negotiated on the connection.
    </para>
    <para>
    This parameter has three possible values:
    <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
            <para><constant>Yes</constant>:
            This setting is for testing purposes.  If SMB3 or above has 
            been negotiated on the connection, and if Persistent Handle 
            support has also been negotiated on the connection, then the 
            server will indicate CA support on the share in the Tree Connect 
            response whether or not the underling file system actaully
            supports CA.
            </para>
        </listitem>
        <listitem>
            <para><constant>Auto</constant>:
            This setting automatically determines whether or not the share
            supports Continuous Availability.  The following conditions
            must be met:
            <itemizedlist>
                <listitem><para>The negotiated protocol on the connection must
                be SMB3 or above.</para></listitem>
                <listitem><para>Persistent Handle support must have been
                negotiated on the connection.</para></listitem>
                <listitem><para>A Samba VFS module that provides Continuous
                Availability support must have been loaded on the
                share.</para></listitem>
            </itemizedlist>
            If these conditions are met, then the server will indicate CA
            support for the share in the Tree Connect response.  The VFS
            module is then responsible for providing that support.
            </para>
        </listitem>
        <listitem>
            <para><constant>No</constant>:
            Explicitly disables CA support on the share.  The server will 
            not indicate CA support to the client and will not provide 
            Persistent Handles for files that are opened within the share.
            </para>
        </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
    </para>
</description>

<related>persistent handles</related>

<value type="default">auto</value>
</samba:parameter>
